Are you insane?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Shut up!
اسكت!
What are you looking at? Don't want to come up?
ماذا تنظر إليه؟ ألا تريد الصعود؟
How come you're here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
The situation downstairs can't hold him for long.
الوضع في الطابق السفلي لن يصمد طويلاً.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
You've got guts now, huh?
أصبحت شجاعاً الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Running away from home?
هل تهرب من المنزل؟
A stray dog like you,
كلب ضال مثلك،
where can you go?
إلى أين يمكنك الذهاب؟
If I hadn't bumped into Lin Mojiao's car today,
لو لم أصطدم بسيارة لين موجياو اليوم،
do you think you could have escaped unharmed?
هل تعتقد أنك كنت ستنجو دون أن يصيبك أذى؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I will repay this favor
سأرد هذا الجميل
to you in the future.
إلى اللقاء في المستقبل.
Don't wait until another day.
لا تنتظر حتى يوم آخر.
Let's do it today.
فلنفعل ذلك اليوم.
I want to eat noodles.
أريد أن آكل نودلز.
Okay.
تمام.
The same red mole.
نفس الشامة الحمراء.
At tomorrow's bidding meeting,
في اجتماع تقديم العطاءات غداً،
Lin Mojiao will definitely make a move.
من المؤكد أن لين موجياو ستقوم بخطوة.
What you need to do is stay calm.
ما عليك فعله هو أن تحافظ على هدوئك.
[and be prepared for anything.]
[وكن مستعداً لأي شيء.]
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It was you who killed me.
أنت من قتلني.
My son.
ابني.
Killing us wasn't enough,
لم يكن قتلنا كافياً،
you even wanted to kill your brother.
بل إنك أردت قتل أخيك.
Lin Mojiao,
لين موجياو,
we three will take you away now.
سنأخذك نحن الثلاثة الآن.
It was you
كنت أنت
who killed me.
من قتلني؟
You all deserve to die.
جميعكم تستحقون الموت.
You all should die!
يجب أن تموتوا جميعاً!
[Dear guests,]
[أيها الضيوف الأعزاء،]
[ladies,] [and gentlemen,]
[سيداتي،] [وسادة،]
[good morning.]
[صباح الخير.]
[Next, please welcome the president of Lanhe Group,]
[بعد ذلك، يرجى الترحيب برئيس مجموعة لانهي]
[Ms. Lan Hewei,]
[آنسة. لان هيوي،]
to announce the results
لإعلان النتائج
of the resort project bidding.
من عملية تقديم العطاءات لمشروع المنتجع.
Please welcome.
أهلاً وسهلاً بكم.
The company that won the bid
الشركة التي فازت بالمناقصة
for the Lanhe Group's resort project is...
بالنسبة لمشروع المنتجع التابع لمجموعة لانهي...
Vivi.
أنت حي.
[Why are there two President Lans?]
[لماذا يوجد رئيسان يحملان اسم لان؟]
[Could the one on stage] [be a fake?]
[هل يمكن أن يكون الشخص الموجود على المسرح] [مزيفاً؟]
Don't you have
أليس لديك
anything you want to explain to me?
هل هناك أي شيء تريد أن تشرحه لي؟
While I was unconscious,
بينما كنت فاقداً للوعي،
you disguised yourself as me,
لقد تنكرت في هيئتي،
got close to my husband,
تقربت من زوجي،
and then set him up,
ثم نصب له فخاً،
taking over Blue Crane
الاستحواذ على بلو كرين
and suppressing the Lin Group.
وقمع مجموعة لين.
How do you explain
كيف تشرح
all of this?
كل هذا؟
It's not like that.
الأمر ليس كذلك.
We grew up together.
لقد نشأنا معاً.
I had no idea you were this capable.
لم أكن أعلم أنك بهذه الكفاءة.
You really opened my eyes.
لقد فتحت عيني حقاً.
My dear sister.
أختي العزيزة.
Xu Meng...
شو منغ...
She's Xu Meng? Really?
هل هي شو مينغ؟ حقاً؟
Xu Meng
شو منغ
is dead, isn't she?
ماتت، أليس كذلك؟
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
don't believe him.
لا تصدقه.
He's lying to you.
إنه يكذب عليك.
Let's go. I'll explain everything to you.
هيا بنا. سأشرح لك كل شيء.
As the real chairman
بصفته الرئيس الحقيقي
of Lanhe Group,
من مجموعة لانهي،
I hereby announce
أعلن بموجب هذا
that the resort project
أن مشروع المنتجع
of the Blue Crane Group
من مجموعة بلو كرين
will be officially handed over to the Lin Group.
سيتم تسليمها رسمياً إلى مجموعة لين.
As for you,
أما أنت،
the harm you've caused to us
الضرر الذي ألحقته بنا
and the Lin Group,
ومجموعة لين،
I will make you pay for it.
سأجعلك تدفع ثمن ذلك.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
don't trust him.
لا تثق به.
Lin Mojiao is the one who wants to hurt you.
لين موجياو هي من تريد إيذاءك.
I didn't betray you.
لم أخنك.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
trust me.
ثق بي.
can you come out and see me?
هل يمكنك الخروج لرؤيتي؟
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
don't you want to see her?
ألا تريد رؤيتها؟
I heard she got hurt overseas
سمعت أنها تعرضت للأذى في الخارج
and hasn't recovered yet.
ولم يتعافَ بعد.
Vivi, don't trust him.
فيفي، لا تثقي به.
Can you come out and see me?
هل يمكنك الخروج لرؤيتي؟
Vivi.
أنت حي.
If I hadn't seen her get plastic surgery
لو لم أكن قد رأيتها تخضع لعملية تجميل
to look like me,
أن أبدو مثلك،
I would have thought you were lying to me.
كنت سأظن أنك تكذب عليّ.
I have scars on my face.
لدي ندوب على وجهي.
Please respect me.
أرجو أن تحترمني.
This is so interesting.
هذا مثير للاهتمام للغاية.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why am I locked up here?
لماذا أنا محبوس هنا؟
If you want money,
إذا كنت تريد المال،
just name a price.
حدد السعر فقط.
Send it to the Lan family.
أرسلها إلى عائلة لان.
Weiwei,
ويوي,
Don't you remember?
ألا تتذكر؟
I'm your husband.
أنا زوجك.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
I don't know you at all.
أنا لا أعرفك على الإطلاق.
You really don't remember anything?
ألا تتذكر أي شيء حقاً؟
Senior,
كبير،
I haven't been to
لم أزر
Blue Crane since I came back.
بلو كرين منذ عودتي.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكراً لجهودكم المبذولة.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
leave it to me.
اترك الأمر لي.
I want to restart
أريد إعادة التشغيل
the resort project,
مشروع المنتجع،
and
و
we'll handle it all ourselves.
سنتولى الأمر برمته بأنفسنا.
Why are you slandering my sister like this?
لماذا تشوهون سمعة أختي بهذه الطريقة؟
I won't believe a word you say.
لن أصدق كلمة واحدة مما تقول.
Xu Meng wouldn't do this.
شو مينغ لن يفعل هذا.
Fine,
بخير،
then watch for yourself
ثم شاهد بنفسك
if what I'm saying is true.
إذا كان ما أقوله صحيحاً.
She treated me like this
لقد عاملتني هكذا
and almost cost you a big project.
وكاد ذلك أن يكلفك مشروعًا كبيرًا.
Why should I care about her?
لماذا عليّ أن أهتم بها؟
Fine.
بخير.
We'll leave her be.
سنتركها وشأنها.
You should get some rest.
يجب أن تحصل على بعض الراحة.